Finding Aid for the Stanley Kramer Papers LSC.0161
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Awards and Memorabilia
  - University Women of the University of Judaism, trophy, 1976. (Box 366)
    (reboxed as noted below; numbered 363 and 367)
  - Wisdom Society's Award of Honor. (Box 357)
  - World Peace Commendation Award, 1960. (Box 357)
  - [in Russian], 1973. (Box 280)
  - Parent Magazine plaques for: (Box 121)
    - Home of the Brave. (Box 121)
    - Cyrano de Bergerac. (Box 121)
    - On the Beach., (Total of 3 items) (Box 121)
  - New York University B.S. degree, June 1933. (Box 328)
  - New York University Citation for Outstanding Class of 1933, April 11, 1955. (Box 118)
  - Camp Kent medals. (Box 119)
  - Seventeen magazine Picture of the Month plaques for: (Box 120)
    - The Champion, 1949. (Box 120)
    - Judgement at Nuremberg, 1961. (Box 120)
    - Mad, Mad World, 1964. (Box 120)
    - The Pride and the Passion, 1957. (Box 120)
    - Inherit the Wind, 1960. (Box 120)
    - Guess Who's Coming to Dinner, 1968.; (Total of 6 items) (Box 120)
  - Independent Film Journal plaque for Best Producer-Director, 1956-1957. (Box 123)
  - University of Southern California plaque for membership in the Cinema Circulus, 1967. (Box 123)
  - 18 carat yellow gold Premio David di Donatello statuette. (Box 371)
  - 18 carat yellow gold Premio David Di Donatelli statuette. (Box 371)
  - Gallatin Medal presentation speech, 1968. (Box 328)
  - Personal Memorabilia
    - 16mm print of Kramer's lecture for the APA, 1962. (Box 329)
    - 16mm print of Kramer family, 925 feet. (Box 329)
    - 16mm print of Larry Kramer's family, 1,150 feet. (Box 329)
    - Scrapbooks: Larry Kramer; Stanley Kramer and family; Stanley Kramer pictures. (Box 329)
    - Scrapbooks: (Box 119)
      - Stanley Kramer's family. (Box 119)
      - U.S. Army, World War II. (Box 119)
        See also: Box 329.
    - Personal Awards and Memorabilia
      - Temple University, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, plaque for distinguished Film Matter, Cinematography and Directing, 1968. (Box 339)
      - Photograph: New York Yankees' Babe Ruth at Bat, 1927. (Box 339)
        Missing 1985.
      - Speech by Sidney Poitier to Stanley Kramer re: American Jewish Committee Humanitarian Award,, on poster., 1967 (Box 356)
  - Awards, June 20, 1975.
    - Wood stand for statue (see below). (Box 333)
    - Framed B'nai B'rith Certificate of Membership presented to Stanley Kramer, June 1975. (Box 333)
    - Memorial book of the occasion of Kramer's award, paperback. We Are One. (Box 333)
    - Gold-painted plaster statue of David, 33 height. David Award Honoree, 1975. (Box 333)
      Broken to bits in break-in.
- PART 2: Additions, May 1978.
  Material received from Theatre Arts Department.
  - XI. Miscellaneous Film Productions
    - - Raise the Titanic:
      - 1. MARSTAR TITANIC., (folder) (Box 252)
      - 2. Schiff, Gunther Correspondence., (folder) (Box 252)
      - 3. Loanout agreement. (Box 252)
  - XII. Miscellaneous Folders
    - 1. Academy of Motion Picture Arts & Science--Correspondence. (Box 252)
    - 2. Academy Award Nom. for SK, to date., 1949 - (Box 252)
    - 3. A Miscellaneous A (Box 252)
    - 4. Actors & Agents General. (Box 252)
    - 5. Academy of Television Arts & Sc.--General Correspondence. (Box 252)
    - 6. Columbia Pictures--S of F Andersonville Dinner--agreement, August 17, 1962. (Box 253)
    - 7. Columbia Pic. Kramer, Stanley - Personal Loan, 1967-68. (Box 253)
    - 8. Columbia Pic. Kramer, Stanley--agreement, December 29, 1967. (Box 253)
    - 9. W Miscellaneous W (Box 253)
    - 10. XYZ Miscellaneous XYZ (Box 253)
    - 11. After the Fall. (Box 253)
    - 12. Aladdin. (Box 253)
    - 13. Casey Productions, Incorporated--Minutes of Mettings. (Box 253)
    - 14. Columbia Pictures--Guess - Personal Fin. Situation. (Box 253)
    - 15. Columbia Pictures--Zagon & Schiff Contract Fees, August 17, 1962. (Box 253)
    - 16. Columbia Pictures--Compensation, August 17, 1962. (Box 253)
    - 17. Werner, Oskar--General Correspondence. (Box 253)
    - 18. V Miscellaneous V (Box 253)
    - 19. Valenti, Jack - Gen Correspondence. (Box 254)
    - 20. Variety Club. (Box 254)
    - 21. Universities--General Correspondence. (Box 254)
    - 22. U Miscellaneous U (Box 254)
    - 23. United Artists Corp.--Correspondence. (Box 254)
    - 24. United Artists Corporation--Distributors Domestic & Foreign. (Box 254)
    - 25. University Donations Contemplated (Wisconsin, New York University, Wyoming) Correspondence. (Box 254)
    - 26. T Miscellaneous T (Box 254)
    - 27. Television Special - SK. (Box 254)
    - 28. Speaking Engagements - Requests etc. - GEN. (Box 254)
    - 30. Music--Miscellaneous General. (Box 254)
    - 31. "My Glorious Brothers" General Correspondence (Box 254)
    - 32. Agents, Literary - Stories, Scripts, Ideas, Correspondence--#8. (Box 254)
    - 33. Agents, Literary - Stories, Scripts, Ideas, Correspondence--#9. (Box 255)
    - 34. Agents, Literary - Stories, Scripts, Ideas, Correspondence--#10. (Box 255)
    - 35. Articles, Stanley Kramer - Books, Newspapers, Magazines etc. MISC. (Box 255)
    - 36. American International Pictures, Incorporated. (Box 255)
    - 37. Agents, Publishers & Printed Literature, 1972. (Box 255)
    - 38. AFI, The. (Box 255)
    - 39. Beck, Meyer. (Box 255)
    - 40. B Miscellaneous B (Box 256)
    - 41. C Miscellaneous C (Box 256)
    - 42. Book on S. Kramer by S. Kramer and Donald Spoto. (Box 256)
    - 43. Biography S. Kramer. (Box 256)
    - 44. Crank Letters--General. (Box 256)
    - 45. Donations, Requests--General. (Box 256)
    - 46. Director's Guild--General. (Box 256)
    - 47. D Miscellaneous D (Box 256)
    - 48. Columbia Pictures Corporation--Correspondence. (Box 256)
    - 49. Cine Mobil Systems--Correspondence and Data. (Box 256)
    - 50. Chicano Assoc. for Student Assistance (CASA) - UCLA. (Box 256)
    - 51. Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions--Fund for the Republic, Incorporated). (Box 256)
    - 52. Articles, Interviews, etc. (Box 257)
    - 53. Biographies--S. Kramer. (Box 257)
    - 54. Yamashita Clips & Correspondence., (accordion folder) (Box 257)
    - 55. Earl Kramer. (Box 257)
    - 56. Karen Kramer (Sharpe). (Box 257)
    - 57. Academy Awards & Nominations. (Box 257)
    - 58. Tearsheets (3). (Box 257)
    - 58a. Tearsheets (1). (Box 258)
    - 59. Photos--Champion. (Box 258)
    - 60. Article by S. Kramer about Spencer Tracy. (Box 258)
    - 61. United Artists Corp (COMITAS) - OTB ITW TDO--Financing & distribution agreement. (Box 258)
    - 62. United Artists Corporation--Television Film Sales. (Box 258)
    - 63. United Artists Corporation--6 Pictures--Financing & distribution agreement. (Box 258)
    - 64. Alfred H. Miller Company, Incorporated. (Box 258)
    - 65. Montessori Schools, Incorporated (MMWIPP). (Box 258)
    - 66. Morgan Camera Shop. (Box 258)
    - 67. MPAA (Motion Picture Association of America). (Box 258)
    - 68. Motion Picture Health & Welfare Fund. (Box 258)
    - 69. Motion Picture Relief Fund. (Box 258)
    - 70. Motion Picture Sound Editors. (Box 258)
    - 71. Motion Picture Workshop of Bryant High School. (Box 258)
    - 72. Patrick Murphy. (Box 259)
    - 73. Muscular Dystrophy Association. (Box 259)
    - 74. Musso & Frank Grill. (Box 259)
    - 75. Newsweek. (Box 259)
    - 76. David Orgell. (Box 259)
    - 77. Jurgensen's. (Box 259)
    - 78. Jewish Big Brothers. (Box 259)
    - 79. Jewish War Veterans of the U.S. (Box 259)
    - 80. JDA (Joint Defense Appeal). (Box 259)
    - 81. Robert C. Jones. (Box 259)
    - 82. Journals & Supporting Papers. (Box 259)
    - 83. Mike Kaplan. (Box 259)
    - 84. Kelly Girl Service. (Box 259)
    - 85. Kerr's. (Box 259)
    - 86. King James Steaks. (Box 259)
    - 87. Fern Koenig. (Box 259)
    - 88. L Miscellaneous L (Box 259)
    - 89. K Miscellaneous K (Box 259)
    - 90. Library of Congress, The (Wash., D.C.) (Box 259)
    - 91. Locations--General. (Box 259)
    - 92. King, Joe. (Box 259)
    - 93. Kirkus, Service, Incorporated, The (Virginia) Book Reviews, September 68). (Box 259)
    - 94. Kramer, Earl (S. Kramer Letters) General 9-2. (Box 260)
    - 95. Kramer, Earl (S. Kramer Letters) General K-3 File #2. (Box 260)
    - 96. Job Applications, 1972-1976. (Box 260)
    - 97. Job Applications, 1977. (Box 260)
    - 98. Jackson, Michael--Show Mail. (Box 260)
    - 99. Job Applications, 1967-1971. (Box 260)
    - 100. I Miscellaneous I (Box 260)
    - 101. Independent Financing--General. (Box 260)
    - 102. International Federation of Knights of the Cinema. (Box 260)
    - 103. Interviews - S. Kramer - Radio/TV/Taped/Live/Newspaper/General, etc. (Box 260)
    - 104. Baddy Hackett. (Box 260)
    - 105. H Miscellaneous H (Box 260)
    - 106. J Miscellaneous J (Box 261)
    - 107. Katherine Hepburn--General Correspondence. (Box 261)
    - 108. Golden Door. (Box 261)
    - 109. Glass, George--General Correspondence. (Box 261)
    - 110. Film Festivals--Miscellaneous (Box 261)
    - 111. Ivan Volkman. (Box 261)
    - 112. Apollo Verlag. (Box 261)
    - 113. Vendome. (Box 261)
    - 114. Variety Heart Fund. (Box 261)
    - 115. Variety. (Box 261)
    - 116. U.S.C. (Box 261)
    - 117. U.S. A. - U.S.S.R. - Track Meet. (Box 261)
    - 118. Universal Pictures Company, Incorporated. (Box 261)
    - 119. U.S. Department of Commerce--Bureau of the Census. (Box 261)
    - 120. United Nations Association--U.S.A. (Box 261)
    - 121. United Artists Corporation--Cash Requirements. (Box 261)
    - 122. United Artists Corporation--Miscellaneous Correspondence. (Box 261)
    - 123. Award--B'nai B'rith Man of the Year, 1970. (Box 261)
    - 124. Biographies--Spencer Tracy. (Box 261)
    - 125. Biographies--Katherine Hepburn. (Box 262)
    - 126. Biographies--Sidney Poitier. (Box 262)
    - 127. Biographies--Gary Lockwood. (Box 262)
    - 128. Biographies--Anna Magnani. (Box 262)
    - 129. Stanley Kramer Retrospective. (Box 262)
    - 130. Stanley Kramer Television Documentary. (Box 262)
    - 131. Judgment Television file--David Wolper--Stanley Kramer. (Box 262)
    - 132. Film Inventory. (Box 262)
    - 133. Biographies--Anthony Quinn. (Box 263)
    - 134. B'nai B'rith Testimonial Dinner, February, 1971. (Box 263)
    - 135. Kosherama. (Box 263)
    - 136. Earl Kramer. (Box 263)
    - 137. Stanley Kramer. (Box 263)
    - 138. Lakeside Pharmacy. (Box 263)
    - 139. Lambs Public Gambel. (Box 263)
    - 140. Philip Langnor--A Child is Waiting. (Box 263)
    - 141. Ede Robinson. (Box 263)
    - 142. Roxlom Films, Incorporated. (Box 263)
    - 143. Albert J. Ruben & Company. (Box 263)
    - 144. Synanon Foundation, Incorporated. (Box 264)
    - 145. Petty Cash Reimbursements. (Box 264)
    - 146. Pickwick Bookshop. (Box 264)
    - 147. Mel Pierce Camera. (Box 264)
    - 148. Plaza Hotel--New York City. (Box 264)
    - 149. Samuel Pop & Company. (Box 264)
    - 150. Postmaster. (Box 264)
    - 151. Producer--Written Guild of America--Pension Plan (2). (Box 264)
    - 152. Screen Actors Guild--Producers' Pension Plan & Welfare. (Box 264)
    - 153. Palm Springs Biltmore. (Box 264)
    - 154. Pacific Telephone Company. (Box 264)
    - 155. Parisian Florist. (Box 264)
    - 156. Pathé Laboratories, Incorporated. (Box 264)
    - 157. Gregory Peck. (Box 264)
    - 158. Pension Plan--Motion Picture Industry. (Box 264)
    - 159. Permanent Charities Committee. (Box 264)
    - 160. S. Kramer Corporation--Payroll Account. (Box 265)
    - 161. Directors-Producers Pension Trust Fund. (Box 265)
    - 162. Pacific Title and Art Studio. (Box 265)
    - 163. Occidental Life Insurance - Paid Bills. (Box 265)
    - 164. Larcas Productions, Incorporated Production Account. (Box 265)
    - 165. Larch-Mart Market. (Box 265)
    - 166. Larry Productions, Incorporated. (Box 265)
    - 167. La Scala. (Box 265)
    - 168. Philip H. Leonard. (Box 265)
    - 169. Jerry Lewis' Restaurant. (Box 265)
    - 170. Little, Brown & Company. (Box 265)
    - 171. Lomitas Productions, Incorporated Curtleigh Prod., Incorporated. (Box 265)
    - 172. Scam Restaurant 9000. (Box 265)
    - 173. Dan Scariano. (Box 265)
    - 174. Schwab's Pharmacy. (Box 265)
    - 175. Screen Producers Guild. (Box 265)
    - 176. Saturday Review (subscription). (Box 265)
    - 177. Selected Pictures Corporation (George J. Schaefer). (Box 265)
    - 178. Shays, Incorporated. (Box 265)
    - 179. Ship of Fools--Miscellaneous (Box 265)
    - 180. Show (magazine) Renewal Subscription. (Box 265)
    - 181. Mc Miscellaneous Mc (Box 265)
    - 182. N Miscellaneous N (Box 265)
    - 183. O Miscellaneous O (Box 266)
    - 184. P Miscellaneous P (Box 266)
    - 185. Q Miscellaneous Q (Box 266)
    - 186. Quinn, Anthony--General Correspondence. (Box 266)
    - 187. Russia--General Correspondence. (Box 266)
    - 188. R Miscellaneous R (Box 266)
    - 189. Radio Program for S. Kramer (Perets, O'Connor, etc.). (Box 266)
    - 190. Stanley Kramer Retrospective. (Box 266)
    - 191. S Miscellaneous S (Box 266)
    - 192. Schiff, Gunther--General Correspondence. (Box 266)
    - 193. Solaris / Syntar--New Filmakers. (Box 266)
    - 194. Academy Awards Illustrated 27/28 - 64. (Box 266)
    - 195. Agents, Literary Stories, Scripts, Ideas (File #1). (Box 266)
    - 196. Agents, Literary Stories, Scripts, Ideas (3167-4160). (Box 267)
    - 197. Agents, Literary Stories, Scripts, Ideas (File #2), May-December 1968. (Box 267)
    - 198. Agents, Literary Stories, Scripts, Ideas (File #3), 1969. (Box 267)
    - 199. Agents, Literary Stories, Scripts, Ideas (File #4), 1970. (Box 267)
    - 200. Agents, Literary Stories, Scripts, Ideas (File #5), 1971. (Box 267)
    - 201. Agents, Literary Stories, Scripts, Ideas (File #6), 1972. (Box 268)
    - 202. Agents, Literary Stories, Scripts, Ideas (File #7), 1973. (Box 268)
    - 203. Slender Ama, Incorporated. (Box 268)
    - 204. Smith, Harold J. (Box 268)
    - 205. Sonoma County. (Box 268)
    - 206. Southern California Committee of the Joint Defense Appeal of the American Jewish Committee. (Box 268)
    - 207. The Stadium Club. (Box 268)
    - 208. SK Corporation--Administrative Account. (Box 268)
    - 209. SK Corporation--General Account. (Box 268)
    - 210. Stanley Warner Theatre, Beverly Hills. (Box 268)
    - 211. Rudolph Sternad. (Box 268)
    - 212. Story of a Cheat, The--United Artists Notes. (Box 268)
    - 213. Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee. (Box 268)
    - 214. Stuntmen's Association. (Box 268)
    - 215. Production Report--Ship of Fools. (Box 268)
    - 216. Radin's Liquor Store. (Box 269)
    - 217. Railway Express Agency. (Box 269)
    - 218. Rand - Fields. (Box 269)
    - 219. Realities. (Box 269)
    - 220. Revue Studios. (Box 269)
    - 221. Revue Studios Contract. (Box 269)
    - 222. United Artists Corporation Notes Payable (Inherit the Wind). (Box 269)
    - 223. United Artists Corporation Notes Payable (Judgment at Nuremberg). (Box 269)
    - 224. United Artists Corporation Notes Payable (My Glorious Brothers). (Box 269)
    - 225. Trial Balance, 1965. (Box 269)
    - 226. Trial Balance, 1964. (Box 269)
    - 227. Trial Balance, 1963. (Box 269)
    - 228. Trial Balance, 1962. (Box 269)
    - 229. Trial Balance, 1961. (Box 269)
    - 230. Television Competitive Research, Incorporated. (Box 269)
    - 231. Harvey Tyrrell - Buick (Bill of Sale). (Box 269)
    - 232. Television Time Recordings, Incorporated. (Box 269)
    - 233. Tanner Motor Livery. (Box 269)
    - 234. Tavelman's. (Box 269)
    - 235. Tax Returns. (Box 269)
    - 236. Taylor, Jack--Loan. (Box 270)
    - 237. Tele-Sound Service (Norelco Tape Recorder). (Box 270)
    - 238. The Thallians. (Box 270)
    - 239. Thermo-Fax Sales, Incorporated. (Box 270)
    - 240. Spencer Tracy (Judgment at Nuremberg). (Box 270)
    - 241. Transport TC Clearings. (Box 270)
    - 242. TWA - lines. (Box 270)
    - 243. Adela Rogers St. Johns (Final Verdict). (Box 270)
    - 244. San Fernando Valley Mental Health Association. (Box 270)
    - 245. Saks Fifth Avenue. (Box 270)
    - 246. The Sands. (Box 270)
    - 247. George Glass - S. Kramer Corporation. (Box 270)
    - 248. Horwits, Al--agreement. (Box 270)
    - 249. Larcas Productions, Incorporated--Minutes of Meetings. (Box 270)
    - 250. Larry Productions, Incorporated--Minutes of Meetings. (Box 270)
    - 251. Lomitas Productions, Incorporated--Minutes of Meetings. (Box 270)
    - 252. Morris Agency, W. & S. Kramer--agreement. (Box 270)
    - 253. Revue Studios - S. Kramer Corp.--agreement & Correspondence. (Box 270)
    - 254. Roxlom Films, Incorporated--Minutes of Meetings. (Box 270)
    - 255. Search & Destroy Valley of Hanoi, January 5, 1968. (Box 270)
    - 256. Selected Pictures Corporation Agreement. (Box 270)
    - 257. S. Kramer Corporation--Minutes of Meetings. (Box 271)
    - 258. S. Kramer Productions, Limited--Profit Sharing Plan & Trust--Pension Plan & Trust. (Box 271)
    - 259. S. Kramer Productions, Limited--Minutes of Meetings. (Box 271)
    - 260. Sternad, Rudolph--agreement. (Box 271)
    - 261. Story of a Cheat--agreement of Sale to Yul Brynner. (Box 271)
    - 262. Story of a Cheat - United Artists Corporation--Finance & Distribution Agreement. (Box 271)
    - 263. S. Kramer Corp.--agreements w/ Larcas-Roxlom-Larry-Casey. (Box 271)
    - 264. S. Kramer Corp.--agreements w/ S. Kramer. (Box 271)
    - 265. This Side of Innocence (Armand Deutsch) - Story Productions Limited. (Box 271)
    - 266. United Artists Corporation--Larcas ITAG Pressure Point CIN--Financing & Distribution Agreement. (Box 271)
    - 267. United Artists Corporation--Casey - Mad World--Financing & Distribution Agreement. (Box 272)
    - 268. United Artists Corporation--Larry - My Glorious Brother--Financing & Distribution Agreement. (Box 272)
    - 269. Zagon, Aaron & Schiff--agreement. (Box 272)
    - 270. Ziffren & Ziffren - Tax Consultants. (Box 272)
    - 271. Catering Services. (Box 272)
    - 272. Artists 4 (Bill W.)--Correspondence. (Box 272)
    - 273. California Public Interest Law Center. (Box 272)
    - 274. MPAA (Motion Picture Association of America). (Box 272)
    - 275. M Miscellaneous M (Box 272)
    - 276. MPAA - Eugene Dougherty - Code & Rating Program. (Box 272)
    - 277. Felton, Earl. (Box 272)
    - 278. G Miscellaneous G (Box 272)
    - 279. Film Festivals. (Box 273)
    - 280. Dodgers, Incorporated Los Angeles. (Box 273)
    - 281. E Miscellaneous E (Box 273)
    - 282. F Miscellaneous F (Box 273)
    - 283. Columbia Pictures--S. Kramer Productions, Limited--Zagon etc. Retainer & Fee Agreement, January 12, 1968. (Box 273)
    - 284. 10 Commandments. (Box 273)
    - 285. Los Angeles Chapter of Waif (SK Corporation). (Box 273)
    - 286. Los Angeles County Heart Association. (Box 273)
    - 287. The Luau--SK Corporation. (Box 273)
    - 288. Mac's Liquors (SK Corporation). (Box 273)
    - 289. Magnetic Recorders Company. (Box 273)
    - 290. I. Magnin & Company (SK Corporation). (Box 273)
    - 291. Magnolia Bowling League (SK Corporation). (Box 273)
    - 292. Abby Mann (in re Judgment at Nuremberg). (Box 273)
    - 293. Manufacturers Hanover Trust Company (Judgment at Nuremberg). (Box 273)
    - 294. Martindale's Book Stores, Incorporated. (Box 273)
    - 295. Martin's Ticket Agency. (Box 273)
    - 296. Mary & Joseph League. (Box 273)
    - 297. May Company. (Box 273)
    - 298. Meadow's Travel Agency. (Box 273)
    - 299. New York University. (Box 274)
    - 300. U.S.C. (Box 274)
    - 301. President John F. Kennedy. (Box 274)
    - 302. Thalberg Award, Irving, April 9, 1962. (Box 274)
    - 303. New York University--Gallatin Award (includes stills). (Box 274)
    - 304. DGA. (Box 274)
    - 305. DGA, Film negotiations, 1973. (Box 275)
    - 306. American Film Institute, Seminar, July 1973. (Box 275)
    - 307. Gladney Schrag Communications, 1977-78. (Box 275)
    - 308. Gladney, Norman, Radio spot. (Box 275)
    - 309. Awards, miscellaneous (Box 275)
    - 310. UCLA, 1972. (Box 276)
    - 311. UCLA,, Chancellor's Associates, S. Kramer., 1969-1971 (Box 276)
    - 312. UCLA Univ. Research Lib., Stanley Kramer Donation, S. Kramer., 1970-1971 (Box 276)
    - 313. Bill Mull. (Box 276)
    - 314. Rocket Messenger Service. (Box 276)
    - 315. Stanley Kramer Show. Losers. #2. (Box 276)
    - 316. Stanley Kramer Show. Winners. #3. (Box 276)
    - 317. Kramer clips. (Box 277)
    - 318. Stanley Kramer--Articles and correspondence. (Box 277)
    - 319. Tracy--Clips-features-stories. (Box 278)
    - 320. Stanley Kramer Show--Comedians. #1. (Box 278)
  - 13. Miscellany
    - Books
      - 1. Crichton, Robert. The Secret of Santa Vittoria. (Advance Copy) New York: Simon & Schuster, 1966. (Box 280)
      - 2. Groundswell: University of Bridgeport's Magazine of the Arts. University of Bridgeport, 1977. (Box 280)
      - 3. Man of the Year Award Dinner--Beverly Hills: B'nai B'rith. (Box 280)
      - 4. Klein, Alexander, ed. Natural Enemies. New York: Lippincott, 1969. (Box 280)
      - 5. Porter, Katherine Anne. Ship of Fools. Boston: Little, Brown & Company, 1962. (Box 281)
      - 6. We are One. 1975 David Award. B'nai B'rith. Beverly Hills Hotel, June 14, 1975. (Box 281)
      - 7. Book on Chaplin, Russian language. (Box 281)
      - 8. Book on S. Kramer, Russian language. (Box 281)
    - Periodicals
      - 1. TV Guide, October 30-November 5, 1976. (Box 281)
      - 2. Coronet, April 1969. (Box 281)
      - 3. McCall's, May 1969. (Box 281)
      - 4. Life, February 17, 1969. (Box 281)
      - 5. Life, December 6, 1968.; (cover only) (Box 281)
      - 6. McCall's, July 1967. (Box 282)
      - 7. McCall's, June 1966. (Box 282)
      - 8. Los Angeles, March 1977.; (2 copies) (Box 282)
      - 9. AFI Dialogue on Film, vol. 2, #9, July 1973. (Box 282)
      - 10. Action, May/June 1976. (Box 282)
      - 11. Daily Variety, April 19, 1976. (Box 282)
      - 12. Hollywood Reporter, (2)., September 26, 1969 (Box 282)
      - 13. TV Guide, June 8-14, 1974.; (2 copies) (Box 282)
    - Records
      - 1. Side one: Amazing Grace (from the Television file The Mancini Generation; Side two: Oklahoma Crude. (43), Yellow label. (Box 283)
      - 2. Sides 1 and 2: Oklahoma Crude., Orange label. (Box 283)
    - Scripts and Related Material.
      - 1. Story of a Cheat, The. (3) (Box 282)
      - 2. The Monday Man, by Ronny Pearlman (Second draft:, December 1, 1971). (Box 282)
      - 3. No Alternative, Preliminary draft: (2)., April 23, 1976 (Box 284)
      - 4. No Alternative, (First draft:, May 19, 1976). (Box 284)
      - 4a. No Alternative. Background material and story outline. (Box 284)
      - 5. 40 Days of Musa Dagh, by F. Werfel. (Box 284)
      - 6. Citizen Tom Paine, by H. Fast. (Box 284)
      - 7. Judgment: The Court Martial of General Yamashita, (First tape draft:, February 28, 1974). (Box 284)
    - Tapes
      - 1. George Glass - Guess Who's Coming to Dinner - Reference Dubs - Not for Broadcast; (1) Sidney Poitier (2) Stanley Kramer (3) Cecil Kellaway. (7½) (Box 286)
      - 2. Columbia Pictures--Ivan Volkman, Jim Merrick, May 2, 1967.; (3.75, Side one) (Box 286)
      - 3. Columbia Pictures--G. Cambridge, S. Kramer, May 2, 1967.; (3.75, Side one) (Box 286)
      - 4. Columbia Pictures--S. Kramer, K. Houghton, May 2, 1967.; (3.75, Side one) (Box 286)
  - Transcripts.
    - United States of America vs.. Tomoyuki Yamashita., TRANSCRIPTS.
      - 1. Pages 1-198. (Box 286)
      - 2. Pages 199-449. (Box 286)
      - 3. Pages 450-699. (Box 287)
      - 4. Pages 700-951. (Box 287)
      - 5. Pages 952-1124. (Box 287)
      - 6. Pages 1125-1306 (Box 287)
      - 7. Pages 1307-1500. (Box 287)
      - 8. Pages 1501-1651. (Box 287)
      - 9. Pages 1652-1867. (Box 288)
      - 10. Pages 1868-2062. (Box 288)
      - 11. Pages 2063-2241. (Box 288)
      - 12. Pages 2242-2468. (Box 288)
      - 13. Pages 2469-2703. (Box 288)
      - 14. Pages 2704-2906. (Box 289)